ANNA MAMCHYCH

DATA ANALYTICS DATA SCIENCE MACHINE LEARNING | DEEP LEARNING

✓ annamamch17@gmail.com

- Remote
- in linkedin.com/in/anna-mamchych

+48 690 493 749 | +38 099 026 15 68

https://github.com/AnnnaMm

https://public.tableau.com/app/profile/anna.mmchch

PROFILE

A creative and disciplined individual with a strong background in the arts, having graduated after seven years of study at an art school. I am passionate about continuous self-improvement, regularly attending industry conferences, seminars, and events related to the IT world. Outside of my professional interests, I enjoy strategic thinking through chess, as well as exploring the rich history of Ancient Egyptian mythology. I maintain an active lifestyle, regularly going to the gym, and bring a combination of creativity, problem-solving skills, and dedication to any project or team I am part of.

WORK EXPERIENCE 向

Teacher of English for children

10.2023 - present Remote

 Conducted individual classes for children aged 5-17 years, led conversation clubs and activity clubs (drawing and Minecraft in English), also filled out reports and worksheets.

Trainee (IT department)

06.2023 - 08.2023 PEPCO, Poznań

 Acquired knowledge of processing, transformation, interpretation and visualization of data. Gained experience with EXCEL and ERP. Learned how to use DAX. Practiced using Power BI.

ACHIEVEMENTS &

New Technologies for Women - Ukraine

09.2023 to 06.2024

Poland

• Laureate of the NTDD Ukraine grant program prize sponsored by Intel and Perspektywy.

EDUCATION &

The Adam Mickiewicz University of Poznan | 10.2024 - present

MSc in Mathematics and informatics: Data analysis and processing

The Adam Mickiewicz University of Poznan | 10.2021 - 07.2024

BSc in Mathematics and informatics: Statistics and data analysis

Bsc thesis - Statistical analysis of the impact of the introduction of the "Safe Credit 2%" program on apartment prices in Poland.

The Ivan Franko National University of Lviv | 09.2020 - 06.2024

BSc in Applied mathematics and informatics: System analysis and management. Data

Thesis - Three-step method of minimizing a function in a basis aradient method.

Thesis - Three-step method of minimizing a function in a basis difference analogue of the Davidon-Fletcher-Powell method.

SKILLS SUMMARY

Soft

Flexibility of mind - Attention to details -Critical Thinking - Time Management -Knowledge principles of OOP

Hard

Python - R - PostgreSQL - MongoDB -Tableu - Office programs - HTML/CSS

LANGUAGES

- English above average
- Polish fluent
- Ukrainian fluent

CERTIFICATES

- EF SET Certificate C1
- Google Analytics for Beginners
- Google Analytics Advanced
- MongoDB (13 certificates)